sexygirlswallpapers.info 2009-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Sexy Girls Wallpapers

### Privacy Policy

**Sexy Girls Wallpapers** will never ever ever share or distribute your email address. It is totally safe with us.

**Your Privacy**

sexygirlswallpapers.info is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information To send you the latest updates about the site.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

When you subscribe, we might need to know your name, e-mail address just to send you the updates of our Site.

**What about “cookies”?**

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors yea but we do use Google which use Third Cookies just to present you the best possible and relevant Ads.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Will sexygirlswallpapers.info disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

sexygirlswallpapers.info does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. sexygirlswallpapers.info may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

sexygirlswallpapers.info may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of sexygirlswallpapers.info, our users, or others.

**In Summary**

sexygirlswallpapers.info is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make sexygirlswallpapers.info as simple as possible and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by sexygirlswallpapers.info. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Questions and Feedback**

If you have any questions or feedback related to our Privacy Policy, please email us at info@sexygirlswallpapers.info

Posted under [Uncategorized](http://sexygirlswallpapers.info/category/uncategorized/ "View all posts in Uncategorized")

This post was written by admin on June 29, 2009
